

Personal Information

FIRST NAME / SURNAME

Mitchell Barclay

MOBILE

+64 27 747 2480

EMAIL

mitchellbarclay2@gmail.com

References

WORK:

John Niland

MOBILE:

+64 27 759 6414

CHARACTER:

Lesley Lyver

MOBILE:

+64 27 450 1865

Skills and Competences

SOCIAL SKILLS

I am polite, friendly and easy to get along with. I have experience with customer service from customer orientated jobs at Burger Wisconsin and Countdown.

COMPUTER SKILLS

I am a keen computer user and would consider myself skilled in the field. I am familiar with basic applications such as Microsoft Word and Excel, but I am also a proficient problem solver when it comes to IT. I pick up new interfaces and software intuitively and quickly, and have experience in coding HTML, CSS, Javascript & SQLite.

ART & DESIGN

I am currently studying Media Design at Victoria and have had a passion for art since I was young. I have experience with graphic design, web design, illustration, 2D animation, stop-motion, as well as video design and editing. I am a competent and experienced user of the Adobe suite of applications.

My design portfolio can be found at:

https://mitchellbarclay.github.io/Portfolio/index.html



Education and Training

DATES 2015-Present

QUALIFICATION PROGRESS In fifth and final year

DEGREE Conjoint: Bachelor of Commerce & Bachelor of Design

Innovation

MAJOR Information Systems, Media Design

UNIVERSITY Victoria University of Wellington

ACCOLADES Included on both the Victoria Business School Dean's

List, and the Victoria Faculty of Architecture and Design

Dean's List for the year 2018.

Work Experience

DATES September 2018 - Present

POSITION Night-fill assistant & grocery team member

EMPLOYER Countdown

RESPONSIBILITIES Customer service, stacking shelves, locating product.

DATES December 2018 - Present

POSITION Cruise Security guard

EMPLOYER Allied Security

RESPONSIBILITIES Organising passenger transport, checking passenger

ID, managing bus traffic.

DATES February 2018 - August 2018

POSITION Night cleaner

EMPLOYER Otis & Louie Ltd.

RESPONSIBILITIES General cleaning of pet daycare, prepping dogs for

pickup.

DATES November 2016 - February 2017

POSITION Commercial painter - summer position

EMPLOYER Terry Lynch Decorators

RESPONSIBILITIES Prepping/ painting interior & exterior of houses.

DATES March 2014 - October 2014

POSITION Kitchen help/ food counter attendant

EMPLOYER Burger Wisconsin

RESPONSIBILITIES Customer service, prepping meals, dishwashing.